mygym.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | My Gym

* * *

**1\. Introduction.**

Thank you for visiting the My Gym (“MY GYM”) website ("Site"). This Privacy Policy details certain policies implemented throughout MY GYM and our franchises governing MY GYM’s use of personally identifiable information about customers, potential customers, and users provided to MY GYM via this Site, registration forms for MY GYM’s membership or otherwise provided from our franchisees and third party affiliate entities. 

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE USING THE SITE. By accessing the Site, using the Site or by clicking on a box that states you accept or agree to this Privacy Policy, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following Privacy Policy. This Site is intended for entertainment purposes only and for users 13 years of age or older. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, please make sure to have your parent or legal guardian review and discuss the Privacy Policy with you as well as MY GYM’s Terms of Use and any other legal notices posted on this Site. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy of use and/or not yet 13 years of age, please do not view, access, or otherwise use this Site. 

The terms “MY GYM” or “us” or “we” or “our” refers to Gym Consulting, Inc. dba My Gym Enterprises, the owner of the Site, and its subsidiaries, affiliates, partners, agents, attorneys, officers, directors, employees. The terms “you” or “your” refer to the user or viewer of the Site. The terms “use” or “using” in this agreement refers to any time when an individual (a “user”), directly or indirectly, (a) accesses or attempts to access, displays, views, prints or copies from the Site, (b) receives, transmits or exchanges data with the Site or with the Site’s users, (c) registers an account with the Site or registers for a MY GYM class, schedules a birthday party or purchases any other product or service via the Site, or (d) in any way utilizes, benefits from, or interacts with any feature, function, service of the Site for any purpose. 

* * *

**2\. Privacy Policy Updates.**

Due to the Internet's rapidly evolving nature, MY GYM may need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. MY GYM reserves the right to change, modify, or otherwise alter our Privacy Policy at any time and at our sole discretion without specific notice to you. MY GYM will post any updated Privacy Policy on our Site so you are always aware of what personally identifiable information we may collect and how we may use this information. MY GYM encourages you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of this Site and/or continued provision of personally identifiable information to us or our franchisees will be subject to the terms of the then-current Privacy Policy and shall constitute your acceptance and acknowledgement of the then-current Privacy Policy. 

* * *

**3\. Information Collection and Use.**

You can generally visit our Site without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Site, we may require you to register for an account or a MY GYM class, or we may invite you to submit questions or comments or request information, subscribe to newsletters, and participate in surveys, questionnaires, promotions, sweepstakes or contests. Due to the nature of some of these activities, we may ask that you complete and submit an online form with personally identifiable information such as your name, username, email address, and other contact information. In order to schedule a birthday party or purchase any other product or service through the Site, you may be required to provide a credit card or debit card number, expiration date and authorization code, which is forwarded to our payment processor. You may refuse to submit any personally identifiable information through the Site in which case you can still view certain aspects of the Site but will not be able to participate in certain services offered by the Site. 

We may use your personally identifiable information to enroll your child in a class, deliver certain services, products or information you have requested, verify your authority to enter certain password protected areas of the Site, send you notices for products and/or services that you have used or that may be of interest to you, send you newsletters, and improve the content and general administration of the Site. 

You should not provide any personally identifiable information, register for an account or class, subscribe to newsletters, or participate in surveys, questionnaires, promotions, sweepstakes or contests unless you are at least 13 years of age. 

* * *

**4.Children's Privacy.**

This Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13 years old. MY GYM recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. MY GYM does not target or solicits our services or this Site to children under 13 years of age but rather targets our services and this Site to parents. MY GYM does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 or knowingly permit any children under the age of 13 years old to register with or use the Site. If a user indicates that he or she is under age 13 years old, the user will not be permitted to register with or enter the Site or submit personally identifiable information that would be transmitted to us via the Site. In the event we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 years of age via the Site, we will delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe we have information from or about a child under the age of 13 years old, please contact us immediately by email at: [mperez@mygym.com](mailto:mperez@mygym.com?subject=Privacy). 

* * *

**5\. Cookies.**

We may use small text files called cookies or similar technologies to improve overall Site experience. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the web browser of a user's hard drive. Cookies do not store or contain personally identifiable information. Cookies enable us to “relate” a user’s activities on and visits to our Site. Cookies must be enabled for you to use certain areas of the Site. 

Third party advertisements on the Site may also contain cookies. MY GYM does not control these cookies. Users should review the privacy policy of the third party to determine whether and how the third party advertisers use cookies. 

Users can program their web browsers to warn them every time a cookie is sent. Users can also program their web browsers to refuse cookies. Please note that without cookies users may not have access to certain services or content on the Site. 

* * *

**6\. Aggregate Information.**

The Site may track the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, IP addresses, External Websites (defined below in Section 7) linked to, and we may analyze this data for trends and statistics in the aggregate, but such information will be maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form only and it will not contain personally identifiable information. We may use such aggregate information to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

* * *

**7\. Disclosure.**

We may disclose your personally identifiable information that we collect and the data generated by cookies to our parent, subsidiary or affiliate entities within our corporate family, our franchisees, third party partner entities and the vendors and service agencies that we may engage to assist us. For example, we may provide your personally identifiable information to an organization in order to complete a service (e.g., process your payment). We also provide your personally identifiable information to the franchisee operating the MY GYM location in your area or in which you have scheduled a class or arranged a birthday party or other event. Such third party entities will be restricted from further distributing your personally identifiable information and may be obligated to a written confidentiality agreement that is at least as protective of your personally identifiable information as the terms of this Privacy Policy and they will not be permitted to further distribute your personally identifiable information. However, such third party entities may use your personally identifiable information to send you marketing or promotional materials. We also will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority. We may also disclose your personally identifiable information to enforce the Terms of Use or to protect the safety and security of our users. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to any other company or organization except we may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which MY GYM participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of MY GYM's assets to which this Site relates. 

* * *

**8\. Links to Third Party Sites.**

The Site may provide links to other websites or resources operated by other companies over which MY GYM does not own, operate or control ("External Websites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by MY GYM of those External Websites. You acknowledge and agree that MY GYM is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that MY GYM is not responsible for the content of such External Websites. Your use of External Websites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Websites. You should review the privacy policies and terms of use of any External Websites to determine how these websites collect and/or use your personally identifiable information. 

* * *

**9\. Security.**

We may employ procedural and technological measures, consistent with industry practice. Such measures are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, use, disclosure, alteration or destruction. MY GYM may use firewalls, internal restrictions, password protection and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of your personally identifiable information. 

* * *

**10.Consent.**

Your use including, without limitation, to your provision of personally identifiable information constitutes your consent to our collection and use of your personal information in this Privacy Policy. 

* * *

**11\. Correction/Updating Personally Identifiable Information.**

MY GYM provides you with the ability to review, correct and delete any of the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us. If you wish to review or correct any information you have provided to us, you may contact us by email at: mperez@mygym.com. 

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact us via email at: [mperez@mygym.com](mailto:mperez@mygym.com?subject=Privacy). 

Your California Privacy Rights 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personally identifiable information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 

Mae Perez   
15300 Ventura Blvd., Suite 414   
Sherman Oaks, CA 91403 

Updated: August 15, 2013
